在1945年和1962年之间 美国进行了331次空爆核弹试验
直到今天 美国政府仍然 否认核辐射灰尘会造成基因变化
（新墨西哥州沙漠）
救命！救命 救命
Help me! Help me. Help me.
我的蛋糕做好了
My cake is ready.
时间到了 大家都上场吧
Time for the show. Everybody on stage.
《隔山有眼》
鲁比？
Ruby?
是你吗？
Is that you?
妈的
Goddamn it.
鲁比？
Ruby?
如果是你的话 丘比特 我有大个的枪子儿喂你
If that's you, Jupiter, I got some buckshot for you.
你听到了吗？
Ya hear me?
我告诉你我不干了！
I told you, it's over!
不关我事！你听到了吗？
I'm out! Ya hear me?
你自己看着办吧！
You're on your own now!
我…
I…
对不起 我真受不了了
I'm sorry, I can't do this anymore.
有人吗？
Hello!
嘿
Hey!
- 啊 外面象火炉一样 - 宝贝你应该呆在车里
- Ah! It's hot out here. - Honey, you ought to stay in the car out of the wind.
- 亲爱的 我总得活动一下筋骨 - 怎么一个人都没有？
- Well, honey, I have to stretch my legs. - Where the hell is everybody?
- 有人吗？- 嘿
- Hello? - Hey.
- 起来吧 笨蛋 - 鲍比！
- Get up, jackass. - Bobby!
哦 嘿
Oh. Hey.
- 加满油 再检查一下机油 老兄 - 好 马上就来 先生
- Fill her up and check the fluids, my friend. - Oh, yeah. Right away, sir.
嘿！
Hey!
- 美女 野兽 住口！- 啊！他妈的！
- Beauty, Beast, stop it! - Ah! Ah! Damn it!
你没事吧？
You okay?
再告诉我一遍为什么我们 不能象正常人那样做飞机？
Tell me again why we couldn't fly like normal people? Oh, that's right.
- 哦 原来是他们不让你爸开飞机 - 道格 别说了
- They wouldn't let your dad drive the plane. - Doug, relax, please.
这是他们的银婚纪念 你能来他们很高兴的
It's their silver anniversary, and they're so happy you came.
- 你父母看不惯我 - 不对 你错了 他们喜欢你
- Your parents can't stand me. - Nope, you're wrong. They love you.
我本来可以带他们去海上环游的
I could have taken them on a cruise.
你闭嘴好不好？我从来没有要求过你什么 是不是？
Hey, you know what? Stop. I never ask you for anything, okay?
想想等我们银婚纪念的时候 凯瑟琳来了你会多高兴
Just think how happy you'll be when Catherine comes along on our 25th, huh?
啊 没有事
Aw, it's okay.
在这个烂车里面我才不会高兴呢
It's not gonna be in a fucking trailer home.
这一带的旅游者不多见 你们要去哪里？
Don't see too many travelers around here. Where y'all headed?
- 圣地亚哥 - 加利福尼亚？
- San Diego. - California?
- 嗯 - 这条路够绕远的
- Uh-huh. - Sure didn't take the fastest road.
哦 不 我们是要看沙漠风光
Oh, no. We absolutely had to see the desert.
- 是不是 鲍勃？- 当然
- Didrt we, Bob? - Absolutely.
沙漠里什么都没有
There ain't nothir to see in the desert.
真的？你听到了 亲爱的？
Really? Did you hear that, honey?
是的
Yeah.
你不知道在加油泵边上 吸烟是违法的吗？
Don't you know it's illegal to smoke around a gas pump?
嗯
Yeah.
过来过来小乖猪
Come here. Come on. He's a good little piggy.
小乖猪 小乖猪
Little baby piggy. Little baby piggy.
鲍比 过来看看这个
Hey, Bobby, come over here. Look at this.
哦 上帝 真不常见
Oh, my God. That's so random.
你们俩真是天生一对
You two make a perfect pair.
嘿
Hey.
你真乖
You're sweet.
嗯
Yeah.
嘿！你干什么？别在那尿
Hey, what are you doing? Don't pee there.
你管得太宽了吧？转过头去我马上就完
What the hell do you care? Just turn around for a second.
喂 你难道没有看到？
Uh, hello. Don't you see that?
受不了
Geez.
她受不了这种热浪的 我告诉过你要用棉布的尿布
She's so uncomfortable in this heat. I told you to use cloth diapers.
- 妈 医生说这些尿布也很好 - 看她的小脸蛋儿
- Mom, the doctor said these were fine. - Look at those little cheeks.
- 我知道 亲爱的 - 是的 她没事的
- I know, sweetheart. - Yes, she is. It's okay.
我觉得她是又饿了
I think she's getting hungry again.
对不起 你知道哪有电话能用吗？我的手机收不到信号
Uh, excuse me. Do you have a phone I can use? I can't get a signal out here.
不 我不知道
No, I don't.
嘿 布科斯基 你就别玩手机了
Hey, Bukowski. Give the cell phone a rest.
对不起 鲍勃 这是工作电话
Sorry, Bob. Duty calls.
亲爱的 从我们一出发 你就抱着手机讲个没完
Honey, you've been on the phone since we left, really.
亲爱的 我已经出来两天了
Well, sweetheart, I've been gone two days.
我必须要保证我的店一切正常
I have to make sure that my store's not burning to the ground.
上帝
Oh, God.
多谢了 布伦达
Thanks, Brenda.
怎么回事 布伦达？
What the hell, Brenda?
妈的！
Damn it!
妈的！弄得我满手都是！
Damn it! Got it all over my hand.
我们到I-88公路还有多远？
How far are we from I-88?
- 混蛋变态 - 什么？
- Freaking perv. - What?
- 至少5或6个小时 - 你饿吗 宝贝？
- You're at least five or six hours. - You hungry, sweetie?
- 为什么我们不走圣达菲呢？- 那边太乱
- Why couldn't we have gone through Santa Fe? - It's nasty out here.
- 亲爱的 你就不能少说两句？- 如果我这么说…
- Honey, could you put a cork in it for a minute? - Well, if I do say so myself…
女士 你丈夫说得很对
Ma'am, your husband here's quite right.
这是唯一的南下通往I-88的路 从这里…
This is the only southbound road going to l-88. From there…
可以走40号公路 但是绕远而且路面太旧
You can take the 40 to California, but it's a long, old drive.
我无所谓 我喜欢夜里开车
That doesn't bother me a bit. I like to drive at night.
我过去15年的时间 就是夜里巡逻
I used to work the night patrol for 15 years.
是吗？你是警察？
Is that right? You a cop?
- 嗯 是探长 - 谢天谢地 现在不是了
- Well, detective. - Not anymore, thank God.
- 我在开办自己的保安公司 - 啊哈
- I'm starting my own, uh, security firm. - Uh-huh.
你也是警察吗 先生？
You a cop too, mister?
不 我是搞通讯业的 …就是卖手机的
No. I'm in telecommunications. I sell cell phones.
- 在这你可找不到顾客 - 是啊
- You won't find any customers around here. - Yeah, no kidding.
一切都正常 机油没问题
Everything's fine. Oil's okay.
美女 回来吧
Beauty, come back here!
老兄 多少钱？
Hey, buddy. What do I owe you?
哦 46美元
Uh, $46 even.
哦 鲍勃 我来付吧
Oh, hey, Bob, here. Let me take care of that.
我还付得起油钱 布科斯基 不用找钱了 朋友
I can still afford the gas, Bukowski. Keep the change, my friend.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I meant.
美女？
Beauty?
美女 出来
Beauty? Come on, girl.
美女？
Beauty?
美女？出来吧
Beauty? Come on, girl.
有人吗？
Hello?
谁在那？
Is anyone there?
美女
Beauty!
美女 你在干什么？
Beauty, what are you doing?
- 我能帮你吗 小姐？- 哦 真对不起
- Can I help you, miss? - Oh, I'm sorry.
是我们的狗 她出去溜哒 然后就不肯安静下来
It's just our dog. She just… She got out, and she won't stay put.
- 琳恩 我们要走了！- 来 小姑娘 我们走
- Lynn, we're leaving! - Come on, girl. Let's go.
鲍比 她总是想出去
Bobby, she keeps getting out.
- 好了 她没事了 - 好
- It's all right. I got her. - Okay.
哦 亲爱的 你能告诉他 别太急吗？
Oh, honey? Honey? Could you, uh, tell him to take it easy?
- 热得我头晕脑涨 - 我们出发
- The heat's making me nauseous. - Let's go!
你要什么吗？
Do you need something?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
我们走 我们走 我们走
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go!
亲爱的 我们现在是在度假
Honey, we're on vacation.
怎么？
Yeah?
你知道…
You know, uh…
地图上没有标 不过
It's not on the map, but if you…
离这两英里的地方 你左转上那条土路
Take a left at the dirt road, couple miles from here…
- 呃 - 就可以穿过山脉
- Uh-huh. - It'll lead you through the hills.
可能省几小时的路程
Probably save you a couple ofhours.
很容易找 在前面有很破旧的栅栏
Can't miss it. Uh, there's an old fence right in front.
谢谢你 非常感谢
Well, thank you. Thank you very much.
旧栅栏 土路 两英里
Old fence, dirt road, two miles.
祝你一路平安
Mm-hmm. You have a safe trip.
谢谢
Thank you.
爸 我讨厌你唱歌
Dad, I hate your singing.
求你们了
Guys, no.
- 别唱了！- 想像一下第一个穿越沙漠的人
- Stop! - Imagine the first people to cross this desert.
他们不知道身在何处
They didn't know where they were.
- 是 我明白 因为我们也不知道身在何处 - 布伦达 路就在这
- Yeah, I can, because neither do we. - Brenda, the road is here.
有路 路就一定通到什么地方
It exists. It's got to go somewhere.
另外 看看风景多好 看那岩石上的光
Besides, look how beautiful it is. Look at the light on the rocks.
真漂亮
It's gorgeous.
- 真操蛋！- 你说什么？
- This is so fucked! - Excuse me?
不许污言秽语 小姐
Watch your language, young lady.
没有人支持我吗？
I would like a little backup here.
- 都是他妈的什么事！- 嘿！管好你的臭嘴！
- This is such bullshit. - Hey, watch your fucking mouth!
我们都冷静下来好不好？大家都累了 是不是？
Can we just calm down here? We're all a little tired, okay?
妈 你难道不是60年代成长起来的吗？为什么还这么道貌岸然？
Yeah, Mom. Didrt you grow up in the '60s? Why are you so uptight?
你妈妈才不是道貌岸然呢
Your mom didn't used to be uptight.
- 她原来可是嬉皮士 - 不是
- She was a little hippie chick. - No.
你要是看到她象你这么大的时候 她可是个小美女
You should have seen her when she was your age. She was a little hottie.
- 爸 - 别瞎说
- Dad. - Stop that.
在炎炎夏日开车穿越 新墨西哥的沙漠
Driving through the New Mexico desert in the middle of summer…
车里的空调还正好坏了
With a broken air conditioner.
真是很棒的假期
Great vacation.
真高兴你来了 要不然我就他妈的的闷死了
I'm glad you came because I would have been so fucking bored otherwise.
是啊 真闷
Yeah. So bored.
哦 你省省力气吧
Oh. Give up on that, man.
我鼓捣了一个半小时 那东西太旧了
I tried for an hour and a half. Thing's ancient.
电线都是中世纪的 早就该换了
Wiring's medieval. Needs to be replaced.
好了
There.
是调温器的问题
There. It's just the, uh, thermostat.
线松了
It's disconnected.
不管怎样 总算可以喘口气了
Anyway, at least we can breathe now.
嘿 我以为你戒烟了
Hey, I thought you quit smoking.
- 我姐知道吗？- 嘿
- Does my sister know? - Hey, man.
我操你姐姐
Fuck your sister.
你知道大块头鲍勃会很不高兴
You know, uh, Big Bob'd get pretty pissed off…
如果他知道你在他的新装修的 88年Airstream车里面抽烟
If he found out you were smoking in his newly renovated '88 Airstream.
- 是吗？- 嗯
- Yeah? - Mm-hmm.
那我连他也一起操
Well, fuck Big Bob too.
给 来一根
Here. Want one? Go ahead.
如果你抽了这烟 你姐非把我阉了不可
Your sister would cut my nuts off if you start smoking.
我以为她很久以前就这么做了呢
I think she did that a long time ago.
你说得不错
I think you're right.
我觉得我们是在这条蓝色路上
I think we're somewhere on this blue road.
妈 我们不在蓝色路上 也不在其他任何路上
Mom, we're not on the blue road or any other road.
那人说这条路不在地图上 还记得吗？
The guy said it wasrt on the map, remember?
我的天！
Oh, my God!
老天！抓紧！
Jesus! Hang on!
照顾好孩子！
Watch the baby!
亲爱的？孩子在哪？
Honey? Where's the baby?
- 她就在这 - 她没事吧？
- She's right here. - Is she okay?
- 没事 没事 - 到底出什么事了？
- She's fine. She's fine. - What the hell happened?
- 太热了 所以轮胎爆了 - 你怎么样？
- The heat must have caused a blowout. - Are you okay?
我还好 还好 就是吓了一跳
Yes, I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm just a little scared.
鲍比呢？鲍比你怎么样？有没有事？
Where's Bobby? Bobby. Are you all right, honey? Are you okay?
他没事
He's all right.
我原来就知道这对孩子不安全
I knew this wasrt going to be safe for the baby.
- 你们怎么样？- 我们还好 没有事
- You okay? - Yeah, we're okay. We're fine.
真混蛋！
Son of a bitch!
- 好了 好了 没有事 - 老天 整个车都坏了！
- Okay, okay, we're all right. - Oh, my God. The whole trailer.
过来 大家来啊
Come here, guys. Come here.
美女！
Beauty!
野兽！
Beast!
真倒霉透顶
We are so fucked.
- 有信号吗？- 什么都没有
- Did you find a signal? - No. Nothing.
全国97%的地方是手机信号覆盖区 我们就在那另外的3%
Ninety-seven percent nationwide coverage, and we find ourselves in that three percent.
- 是的 - 好 你爸要看沙漠风光 我希望这回他可以看个够
- Yeah. - Well, your dad wanted to see the desert. I hope he's enjoying himself.
道格 你又开始了
Doug, don't start.
- 也许这里有人想租个警察呢 - 道格！
- Maybe somebody will need a rent-a-cop around here. - Doug!
- 怎么？- 好了
- What? - Come on.
他可是一有机会就损我 难道我就不能反咬他一口？
Every chance the guy gets, he takes me down a peg. Can't snap back at him?
好了 你还和他一般见识
Yeah, well, don't stoop to his level. It's my fault?
200度的气温！是大家的错
200 degrees out here! It's everybody's fault.
- 别听他的 - 你消停一会儿吧
- Don't listen to him. - Get off my back.
将军 受损程度如何？
General, what's the damage?
轴断了 车报废了
The axle is broken, and it's… totaled.
我们能修吗？
Can we fix it?
什么？
What?
不能 车身都七扭八歪 我们不能…
No, the frame is twisted to hell. We can't…
- 用什么修？我说… - 她在这
- With what? I mean… - There she is.
把手机给我 我得叫个拖车
Give me your damn cell phone. I'm gonna call a tow truck.
没有信号 我试过
No signal. I tried.
- 那么 我们可以使用无线电 - 你可以试 不过我怀疑没有人会听到
- Well, we can use the C. B. - You can try it, but I doubt you're gonna get anybody.
高速公路在山的那一边 你收不到信号的
The freeway's way the hell on the other side of those hills. You won't get a signal.
那么我们怎么办？
So, what are we gonna do?
借过一下
Excuse me.
鲍勃？你在干什么？
Bob? What are we doing?
我们用腿走
We walk.
- 用腿走？- 是的 你和我
- We walk? - Yep. You and me.
我们在沙漠中间 无论去哪里都很远
We're in the middle of the desert. We're miles from anywhere.
不走的话 就守株待兔 等人开车经过吧
It's either that, or we sit here and wait for somebody to drive by.
我们下了高速公路以后 你看到任何人经过了吗？
Have you seen anybody drive by since we got off the freeway?
从你抄近路开始 我就没有看到一个人影
I haven't seen anyone drive by since you decided to take the shortcut.
- 亲爱的 我们一起走走 好不好？- 好吧
- Honey. Honey, let's go for a walk. Okay? - Okay.
那什么都没有 你真是昏头了
There's nothing there, you shitheads.
好 不错 好孩子
There you go. Ah, good boy.
我确信沙漠里到处是响尾蛇 那锁好了吗？
I'm sure this desert is full of rattlesnakes. Is that locked?
- 鲍比 过来 - 我想是锁好了
- Bobby, come here. - I think that's locked.
- 过来 - 好的
- Come here. - Yes, sir.
- 谢谢你 亲爱的 - 不用谢
- Thanks, honey. - You're welcome.
- 你知道 我看过…妈？- 什么？
- You know, I saw… Mom? - What?
- 保险上着呢 - 是 先生
- Safety's on, boy. - Yes, sir.
- 我看过一个关于沙漠里的蛇的纪录片 - 嗯
- I saw a documentary on desert snakes… - Uh-huh.
在「探索」频道 有些种类的
On the Discovery Channel… And there's some species…
咬了你的话 25分钟内人就死了
If you get bit, you can die within like 25 minutes.
是吗？我倒要看看 它们怎么对付这支枪
Really? I'd like to see how they stack up against this one.
我认为那枪支要锁起来的 亲爱的
I thought those were gonna stay locked up, honey.
- 我以为你不是跟我说的 - 你没错
- I thought you werert talking to me, honey. - You're right.
放心 亲爱的 我是有执照的专业人士
Relax, honey. I'm a licensed professional.
另外 相对于你的祷告 我更信任我的子弹
Besides, I'd take my bullets over your prayers any day.
唉 你还是老样子
Well, some things never change.
那么碰到蝎子 土狼什么的怎么办？
So, what about, like, uh, scorpions and coyotes and stuff?
赞美上帝 然后把子弹递给我
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition.
嘿 道格 你想试试吗？
Hey, Doug. You wanna try?
- 嘿！别把枪口对着我！- 别怕 保险开着的
- Hey, don't point that at me! - Don't worry, man. The safety's on.
- 鲍比？- 嗯？
- Hey, Bobby? - Yeah?
不要理道格 他是民主党 他不信仰武力的
Leave Doug alone. He's a Democrat. He doesn't believe in guns.
哦 来吧 道格 过来开一枪
Oh. Come on, Dougy. Come here. Just one shot.
能让你感觉有力量 你可能会喜欢的
It makes you feel kind of powerful. You might like it.
我可不这么想 鲍比 也许我会射到自己的脚
I don't think so, Bobby. I'd probably just shoot my foot off.
你知道 他说得很对
You know, he's right.
他可能真会射到自己的脚
He'd probably shoot his foot off.
- 嘿 B - 嘿
- Hey, "B." - Hey.
你怎么样？
How you holding up?
我太激动了
I am thrilled.
是啊 真是够拽的
Yeah. This is a total drag.
嗯 你知道我才不管他们讲什么呢
Yeah, well, you know, I really don't care what they say.
明年我要和朋友们去坎昆
Next year, I am going to Cancun with my friends.
再也不参加这种家庭旅游了
Not going on any more of these little family trips.
嗯 我们全家一起旅游的机会 没有多少了 你知道吧？
Well, we're not gonna have many more of them, you know?
如果你想去坎昆 你知道 你应该先找个工作
And if you want to go to Cancun, you know you're gonna have to get a job.
哦 是啊 你是说象你的工作？
Oh, yeah. What, you mean like your job?
布伦达 我是帮道格管理商店
Brenda, I help Doug out at the store, okay?
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
亲爱的 你能把我的外衣拿来吗？
Honey? Can you bring me myjacket?
我马上就来 亲爱的
I'll be right there, honey.
鲍比！
Bobby!
操蛋！
Fucker!
- 你能给我个糖吃吗？- 不！
- Could you get me a Twinkie? - No!
- 继续往这个方向走 - 是 好
- Just keep walking this direction. - Yeah, fine.
你找出这条路通向哪里 我往回找我们来的路
You find out where the road leads, and I'll head back the way we came.
- 离我远点 - 好 好
- Stay away from me. - All right.
应该是通向什么地方 也许就回到高速公路了
It's gotta lead somewhere. Maybe back to the freeway.
- 你也带枪吗？- 不 亲爱的 不
- Are you taking a gun too? - No, honey, I'm not.
我不需要用枪来寻找帮助
I don't need a gun to find help.
- 我不要这个 - 你需要带帽子
- I don't want this. - You need the hat.
- 把我头型都弄砸了 - 在这谁看你啊？
- It gives me hat head. I don't like it. - Who cares?
- 又不是时装展览 - 好吧 谢谢你
- It's not about fashion. - All right. Thank you.
听着 如果五六英里内找不到帮助 你就回来
Hey, listen. Uh, if you don't find help within five or six miles, just come back.
好吗？
All right?
- 给 亲爱的 - 我去那加油站
- Here, honey. - I'm gonna go to the gas station.
唯一的问题就是 天黑前你根本赶不回来
You're just never gonna make it back by sunset is the only problem.
亲爱的 才八英里而已 我会借用他的车
Honey, it's only about eight miles. I'll borrow the old mars car.
用他的电话 如果他有电话 我会在天黑前领着拖车回来
Use his phone, if he's got one. I'll be back with a tow truck before nightfall.
- 我能和道格一起去吗？- 不行
- Can I go with Doug? - No. Nope.
你在这陪你妈妈和姐姐们 嘿 布伦达
You stay here with your mother and your sisters. Now, hey, uh, Brenda?
听好了 你要听你弟弟的 好吗？
Listen up. Your brother is in charge, all right?
- 所以别逗他 - 我想你出发前我们应该先祷告
- So don't tease him. - I think we should pray before you go.
- 哦 妈！- 布伦达 不求你都不行吗？
- Oh, Mom! - Brenda, is it really so much to ask?
- 好了 - 来吧
- Yes. - Come on.
真是的
Damn it.
我们等着呢
We're waiting.
感谢上帝没有人在看着我们
Thank God no one's watching us.
- 鲍比 - 别闹了 鲍比
- Bobby. - Stop it, Bobby.
- 好了 - 谢谢
- Stop. - Thanks.
请赐福于我们…
Please bless us at this time…
派遣你的守护天使
And send your guardian angels…
来帮助我们走出山谷
To help us to walk through this valley in our faith…
感激我们的主
This, yeah, with the help of thy dear Lord.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
- 好了 - 再见 道格 你多加小心
- Okay. - Bye, Doug. Be careful.
- 一会儿见 - 一会儿见
- See you later. - See you guys in a few hours.
亲爱的 帽子要戴着 好吗？
Honey? Keep the hat on, okay?
- 戴帽子？- 别装像了
- Am I wearing it? - Don't give me that look.
- 你看到我头上的帽子了？- 我爱你
- Do you see it on my head? - I love you.
我也爱你 再见
I love you too. Bye.
小宝宝 你好
Hi, sweetness. Hello.
谁不想再睡了？
Who doesn't want to sleep anymore?
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
请不要把脚放在桌子上
Please take your feet off the table. Honestly.
我们露营并不意味着 你可以象猪一样
Just because we're camping doesn't mean you get to act like a pig.
你知道 亲爱的
You know, honey, really…
你不应该从乳房到奶瓶 换来换去
You shouldn't go from the breast to the bottle.
她这么大了应该习惯于其中一个
At her age, she should get used to one or the other.
妈 多谢你的建议 不过她是我的孩子
Mom, thanks for the advice, but she's my baby.
真不敢相信在你的纪念日 我们却搁浅在鬼才知道的什么地方
I can't believe that we're stranded in the middle of nowhere on your anniversary.
- 嗯 - 你知道如果我们就在大路上开…
- Hmm. - You know, if we just stayed on the main road…
现在我们就到加州了
We'd be in California right now.
我要洗个热水澡 来一杯冰镇的玛格丽塔
What I'd give for a hot shower and a cold margarita.
- 海滩 - 做个按摩
- The beach. - A massage.
- 我就想在真的床上睡一觉 - 是啊
- I'll take a real bed. - Yeah.
- 大麻 - 什么？
- The chronic. - The what?
布伦达
Brenda!
什么？
What?
妈 她说的是大麻
The chronic. It's pot, Mom.
- 啊 啊 谁吸大麻啊？- 是啊 到底是谁
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Who smokes pot? - Yes, exactly.
- 谁吸大麻？- 嘿 谁看到我的红色运动衫了？
- Who smokes pot? - Hey, has anybody seen my red sweatshirt?
你知道 后座那件带帽子的？布伦达？
You know, the hoodie thing in the backseat? Brenda?
- 你不是坐在上面睡觉了吗？- 我没有碰你的臭运动衫 行了吗？
- Werert you sleeping on it? - I haven't touched your smelly sweatshirt, okay?
为什么狗这么激动？
Why are the dogs so excited?
可能是附近有响尾蛇
There's probably some rattlesnakes somewhere around.
你知道你总是提到响尾蛇 那么弗洛伊德会怎么分析你吗？
You know how Freud would have interpreted your obsession with rattlesnakes, Mom?
鲍比！
Bobby!
太坏了
So bad.
- 鲍比！闭嘴吧 - 太恶心了
- Bobby Can'ter! Stop that! - That's gross!
- 真不应该那么说 - 是有些恶心 我道歉
- That's so wrong. - That was a little gross. I'm sorry.
- 我向在座的所有人道歉 - 好了 谢谢你
- I apologize to the entire table. - Well, thank you.
我真的很高兴 我们能一起旅行
I'm really glad that we all came on this trip together.
啊 是啊 一个大家庭
Ah, well, that makes one of us.
- 水果在哪？- 谁要什么吃的吗？
- Where is the, uh, fruit? - Does anyone need anything?
不
No.
- 嘿 布伦达 - 真太棒了
- Hey. Hey. Brenda! - Wonderful.
- 你搞笑吗？你知道多长时间… - 鲍比
- Are you kidding me? Do you know how long… - Bobby.
- 鲍比？- 对不起
- Bobby? - Sorry.
鲍比 该吃饭了
Bobby, it's dinnertime.
- 我会叫他回来的 妈 鲍比！- 总是这样子
- I'll get him, Mom. Bobby! - This always happens.
鲍比 不要离开车太远
Bobby, I don't want you going away from the trailer right now.
美女！
Beauty!
美女
美女！
Beauty!
我操！
Fuck!
怎么回事？
What the hell?
看看那个
Look at that. Huh.
有人吗？
Hello?
有人在吗？
嘿 老兄
Hey, buddy.
有人在吗？
Hello?
有人吗？
Hello!
嘿 我在你告诉我的近路上 车出了点麻烦
Hey, uh, I had a bit of a wreck out on your, uh, shortcut.
你在吗
Yo!
我拿了一些水 行吗？
I grabbed some water, all right?
电话坏的 妈的
It's dead. Damn it.
朋友！嘿！
Yo, my friend! Hey!
你在这吗？
You here?
你在家吗？
You home?
喂？
Hello?
有人吗？
变态的混蛋
Weird son of a bitch.
嗯
Yeah.
丘比特
Jupiter!
我要喂你枪子尝尝 听到了吗？
I got buckshot, ya hear?
喂 先生
Hey, mister.
你根本不明白这里发生的事情
You don't understand what's going on here.
嘿！
Hey!
孩子们…
The kids…
在矿井里面长大 和野兽一样
Grew up in the mines like wild animals.
打开门 慢慢打开
Open the door, slowly!
对孩子们来说 那是什么样的地方？
What kind of place is that for children?
到底是什么样的地方？
What kind of a place is that?
好了 放下枪 轻轻地放下
Okay. Put the weapon down. Put it down, easy. Put it down.
我已经尽我所能 我很抱歉
I did the best I could. I'm sorry.
嘿！
Hey!
爸爸
Daddy.
爸 爸
Daddy. Daddy.
爸啊爸
Daddy. Oh, Daddy.
爸 爸
Daddy. Daddy.
爸
爸爸
Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy.
布鲁托 把枪给我！
Would you give me that gun, Pluto!
- 把他妈的枪给我！- 你过来！
- Give me the gosh darn gun! - Get on over here!
对了 过来 你不应该有枪的
That's right. Come on. You oughtrt have a gun.
布伦达
Brenda?
布伦达！
Brenda!
我在这！马上就回来！
Hey, I'm here! I'll be back in a minute!
鲍比！
Bobby!
鲍比
鲍比！
Bobby!
鲍比
鲍比！
Bobby!
好 让我来… 亲爱的 头发都…
Okay, let me just… Oh, honey, the hair.
就是有些…
It's just…
你知道布伦达能发现你 是你太走运了
You know, you really are so lucky that Brenda found you.
我是说如果你在外面 饥寒交迫度过一夜怎么办？
I mean, what if you'd had to spend the whole night out there in the cold?
鲍比不要担心 美女饿了就会回来的
Hey, Bobby. Don't worry. Beauty will come back when she's hungry, okay?
- 你试…试了无线电吗？- 根本就不好用
- Did you… Did you try the radio? - It doesn't work.
但是我们听到有些 象是呼吸的声音
But we heard something. Some sort of breathing.
什么呼吸？
What breathing?
很怪异的 是不是 妈妈？
It was weird. Right, Mom? L…
我觉得一定是静电干扰
I'm sure it was just static.
妈！那听起来就象是 变态的搔扰电话
Mom! It sounded like a perverted call.
只有妈妈才会在这里也接到色情电话
Only Mom would get an obscene phone call out here.
鲍比！怎么…
Bobby! What…
- 亲爱的？- 不不不！你们不要出去！
- Honey? - No, no, no, no! I want you guys to stay here.
他怎么了？
What is wrong with him?
他在干什么？
What's he doing?
妈的
Shit.
野兽！野兽！
Beast! Beast!
- 嘿 鲍比 - 老天！
- Hey, Bobby. - Jesus Christ!
啊！别用枪对着我！
Hey! Whoa, whoa! Stop pointing the gun at me! Please!
- 老天！鲍比你怎么… - 道格 真对不起
- Jesus, Bobby! - Doug, I'm sorry, man.
是我 你没事吧？
It's me! You okay?
- 没事 - 老天
- Yeah. - God!
- 不是想吓唬你 - 我知道 不过…
- Didrt mean to startle you, man. - Yeah, I know. I just…
知道吗 我发现了一个地方 你可能都不信 就象是异度空间
Look, I found this place out here. You wouldn't believe it. It's like the Twilight Zone.
- 嘿 - 是鲍勃？
- Hey. - Is that Bob?
- 是道格 没事 - 回来了
- It's Doug. It's okay. - Ta-da!
亲爱的！老天！感谢上帝你没有事！我心里一直都七上八下
Honey! Oh, my God! Thank God you're okay. I was so worried about you.
- 我没事 就是累坏了 - 好吧
- No, I'm fine. Just exhausted. Look. - Yeah.
看看我找到的东西
Look at all this stuff I found.
那边有一个大的火山口
There's a huge crater out there.
人们一定是把那当垃圾场了 我以前从来没有看到过那种地方
People must use it as a dump site. I've never seen anything like it in my life.
- 什么… - 看看这个 还是全新的
- What are… - Look at this stuff. It's brand new.
我们在沙漠里面拿着鱼竿 钓什么好呢？
What are we gonna do with a fishing pole in the desert?
- 我以为你是去找人帮忙 - 走了五英里路就到了尽头
- I thought you went to go find somebody. - Road dead-ends in five miles.
然后就是火山口 根本不是近路 而是沙漠
That's where the crater is. It's not a shortcut. It's just desert.
- 死路？- 死路
- It dead-ends? - Dead end.
- 我知道那个老家伙就在胡说八道 - 希望你爸爸能比我强
- I knew that old man was full of shit. - Hope your dad did better.
也许是我们错过了 该拐弯的地方
Maybe wejust missed a turn.
- 亲爱的你们做什么饭了吗？我饿死了 - 嗯 进来吃吧
- Honey, did you guys cook any dinner? I'm starving. - Yeah. Come on inside.
- 太好了 谢谢 布伦达？- 怎么？
- Great. Thanks. Brenda? - Yeah?
你的唇膏带了吗？我的嘴唇都干了
Do you have that lip balm? My lips are really dry.
你真想用吗？太恶心了 我才不让你用我的唇膏呢
Are you serious? That's gross. I'm not letting you use my lip balm.
你是不是平时不告诉 就用了？
Do you use it without telling me?
等等 鲍比 别关门 我们马上就出去
Wait. Bobby. Don't close that door. We're leaving in a second.
- 什么？- 让你老爸休息会儿吧
- What? - Get some rest for Daddy.
你们不等爸爸回来吗？
You guys aren't gonna wait till Dad gets back?
不 鲍比 我太累了 我要睡一会儿先
No, Bobby, I'm exhausted. I need to get some sleep.
不不不 没关系的 你睡在这儿会很舒服
No, no, no. It's fine. You'll be more comfortable here.
我睡在地板上 妈妈和布伦达到前面去
I'll sleep on the floor, and Mom and Brenda are gonna be up front.
你和林恩睡后面 我们的睡袋足够多了
And you and Lynn can take the back. We got extra sleeping bags.
鲍比 你想让六个人睡在 能装三个人的车里面
Bobby, you got six people sleeping in a three-person trailer.
不会舒服的 而且很怪异
It's not comfortable. It's a little bit weird. Okay?
- 亲爱的 你拿水过来吗？- 是的
- Honey, you gonna bring the water? - Yeah.
- 嘿 道格 我能和说句话吗？- 什么事？
- Hey, hey, hey. Doug, Doug. Can I talk to you? - What's up?
- 宝贝 你来吗？- 马上就来
- Baby, you coming? - I'm almost ready.
- 看 是… - 怎么？
- See, uh… - What's going on?
- 嗯 我… - 鲍比
- Uh, when I… - Bobby.
- 不不不 是… - 鲍比 嘿！
- No, no, no, no. It's… - Bobby, hey.
我确信你爸一定会很快回来的 好不好？
I'm sure your dad's gonna be back soon. Okay?
我是说 他可是大块头鲍勃 对不对？
I mean, come on. He's Big Bob, all right?
我保证那些蛇啊蝎子啊都挡不住他
I'm sure it's gonna take more than snakes and scorpions in the night to stop him.
- 好吗？- 借一下光
- Okay? - Excuse me.
- 不好意思 - 你有枕头吗？
- Sorry. - Did you get pillows?
在SUV里面
They're in the S. U. V.
嘿 听我说
Hey, hey, listen.
如果他在午夜前还没有回来 我们就一起去找他 行吗？
If he's not back by midnight, we'll both go looking for him. Deal?
- 好吧 - 就这样
- Yeah. Deal. - Okay.
- 好好休息 - 晚安 鲍比
- Get some rest, man. - Good night, Bobby.
晚安
Good night.
你干什么？沙漠里没有蚊子的
What are you doing? There's no mosquitoes in the desert.
亲爱的 蚊子满地跑 看你找不找
Honey, there's mosquitoes everywhere.
野兽
Beast.
野兽？
Beast?
野兽
野兽？
Beast?
野兽
野兽？
Beast?
野兽？过来 好孩子
Beasty? Come here, boy.
野兽
Beast?
嘿 大家起来！
Hey. Guys! Guys!
- 老天！怎么… - 老天
- Oh, good God. What… - Jesus!
- 鲍比 - 什么事 鲍比？
- Bobby. - What is it, Bobby?
- 这里有…有不知道什么东西 - 什么？
- Guys, something… something is going on around here, okay? - What is it?
象是住在山里的人 也许是什么其它东西
There… There are, like, people or something living in those hills.
- 人？鲍比 - 不不不 道格
- People? Bobby. - No, no, no, no. Doug.
- 道格 道格 听我说！- 鲍比 鲍比 你听我说！
- Doug. Doug. Please. - Bobby. Bobby, listen to me!
这是一个兔子不拉屎的地方 没有人住在这些山里
We're in the middle of nowhere, okay? Nobody lives in those hills.
- 美女死了 - 什么？
- Beauty's dead. - What?
我发现了她 她象是…
I found her, and, uh, she was, like…
- 被人开了膛 - 开膛？
- It looked like somebody cut her open, you know? - Cut her open?
是 我刚才也没有说…
Yeah, and l-I didn't want to say anything…
因为我不想吓坏大家 也不想让妈妈伤心
Because I didn't want to scare everyone and I didn't want to get Mom upset.
但是我告诉你 外面很危险 而且爸爸还没有回来
But I'm telling you, there is something going on, okay? And Dad's not even back yet.
好吧 你呆在这 我出去看看
Okay. All right. Stay right there. I'll come check this out.
- 外面还有别人 - 好了 林恩
- We're not alone. - All right, Lynn.
你呆在这 锁上车门 好吗？
You stay here, you lock the car, okay?
别激动 我们会弄清楚怎么回事 告诉我你在哪看到的？
Calm down, man. We're gonna check this out. Now where did you see this?
是时候了！
Now!
是鲍勃
It's Bob.
- 等等 我们不知道是怎么回事 - 是鲍勃！
- Wait. We don't know what that is. - It's Bob!
- 我们不知道那是什么！- 鲍勃！
- We don't know what that is! - Bob!
爸？爸爸
Dad? Dad!
布伦达 看好孩子！
Brenda. Watch the baby!
不！
No!
嘿 小小鸟小小鸟 你是一只小小鸟
Hey, little birdie. Hey, little birdie.
走开！快把你妈拉开！把你妈带走！
Get off! Get your mother out of here! Get your mother out of here!
道格！快点想办法！
Doug! Do something!
起来！是男人才能这么做！
Move! You gotta be a man to do that!
我告诉你走开！所以你就赶快给我滚开！
I told you to move! So, move!
快点！快点！
Now, get! Get!
你下面藏着什么呢？来 给我 哇哈哈哈哈
What you got under there? That's it. Give it to me. Whoo! Whoo!
滚开！
Fuck off!
来吧！
Come on. Yeah!
这不是我的鲍勃！不是我的鲍勃！
It's not my Bob! It's not my Bob!
走吧 妈妈 我们走吧
Come on, Mom. No! Let's go. No, just come on.
不是我的鲍勃
It's not my Bob.
那是什么？
What was that?
妈妈 你在这别动 好吗？
Mom, just stay here, okay?
救命！救命！
Help! Help! Help!
哦 你白白胖胖
Oh, you fat.
哦 白白胖胖
Oh. Big, fat…
看起来很好吃
And juicy.
不！不！求你了！
No. No, please!
鲍比！鲍比 你去哪？
Bobby! Bobby, where you going?
我要杀光那些他妈的混蛋！
Fucking kill those motherfuckers!
你回来！别做傻事！
Get back here! Don't do something stupid!
不！不！
No. No.
回车里去！
Get back to the trailer!
快点！出去！
Come on! Get out the door!
救命！开枪射他！快开枪！
Help! Shoot him! Shoot him!
- 布伦达！- 鲍比！
- Brenda! - Bobby!
来吧 看着我 看着我
Come on, now. Look at me. Look at me.
好了 看着我
That's it. Look at me.
妈的！我会回来找你的
Shit! I'll come back for ya.
布伦达！
Brenda!
小泼妇象是疯了一样反抗！
Bitch stuck me like a pig!
你怎么样？你怎么样？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
不
No.
老天！
Oh, God!
别动！别动！亲爱的 别动！
Don't move! Don't move, honey. Don't move.
好了 好了 你会没事的
Okay. Okay. All right. You're gonna be okay.
你会好的 亲爱的
You're gonna be okay. S-Sweetheart?
会好的
Okay.
亲爱的？宝贝？
Honey? Sweetheart?
林恩！坚持！
Lynn, come on!
林恩！
Lynn!
醒来吧
Come on!
好
Okay.
我们应该做什么？啊？我们…
What are we gonna do? Huh? What are we…
我们怎么办？我们…
如果他们回来 我们该怎么办 道格？
What are we gonna do if they come back, Doug?
这个车太小了 我清洗了一遍又一遍
This trailer is so small. I clean and clean.
- 还是一团糟 - 嘘
- It's still a mess. - Shh.
一团糟
It's a mess.
- 大块头鲍勃回来了吗？- 还没有
- Is Big Bob home? - Not yet.
大家…大家都睡了吗？
Every… Everybody went to bed?
- 是吗？- 是
- Yes? - Yeah.
布伦达就在这 鲍比在后面
Brenda's right here, and Bobby's in the back.
林恩睡了吗？
Is Lynny sleeping? Hmm?
你需要什么吗？
You need anything?
- 给我个毯子 - 好的
- A blanket. - Okay.
- 真冷 - 好的
- It's cold. - Okay.
- 真冷啊 - 嘘…这回就暖和了
- It's cold. - Shh. Shh. Nice and warm, huh? Nice and warm.
你真是好孩子 道格
You're so sweet, Doug.
我知道为什么林恩那么爱你了
I understand why Lynny loves you so much.
那么
So…
我再也受不了了！
I'm not gonna take this shit.
- 嘿 我们不能出去！你想死吗？- 我他妈的豁出去了！
- Hey, we're not going anywhere! You wanna die too? - I don't fucking care!
你豁出去了？看看他们对你妈妈下的手！
You wanna die, huh? Look what they did to your mother!
看看他们对你姐姐下的手！你停下来好好想想！
Look what they did to your sister! Huh? You stop and think!
你他妈的不再是小孩了！你要是出去只能血溅当场！
You're not a fucking child anymore! You won't make it three feet out there.
我们要有计划 要好好想
We need a plan. We need to think.
- 我们需要…想 - 想什么？
- We need… We need to think. - Think about what?
想什么 道格？他们抓走了凯瑟琳！
Think about what, Doug? They have Catherine!
他们抓走了你的女儿 而你就坐在这里无动于衷？
They have your daughter. And you're just gonna sit here and do nothing?
因为你就是一个胆小鬼！我爸爸说得真没错！
That's 'cause you're a fucking pussy just like my dad said!
- 你他妈的给我闭嘴！闭嘴！- 去你妈的！
- Shut the fuck up! You shut up! Shut your mouth! - Fuck you.
不！把灯打开！
No! Turn the lights on.
把灯打开 把灯打开
Turn the lights on. Turn the lights on.
- 他说了他会回来！- 嘘！安静
- He said he's coming back! - Shh! Quiet!
他说了他会回来找我
He said he's coming back for me. Please.
是他们！是他们！是他们！
It's them! It's them! It's them!
风镜？风镜？
Goggle? Goggle?
风镜？你收到了吗 风镜？
Goggle? You copy, Goggle?
风镜在哪？
Where's Goggle?
他留在那里监视他们
He stayed back there. He's keeping an eye on them.
- 我告诉过你 - 什么？
- I told you. - What?
我告诉过你应该把他们杀光！
I told you, you've gotta kill them all!
野兽！野兽！你还活着！
Beast! Beast! You're alive!
哦 好孩子！好孩子好孩子
Oh, good boy. Good boy. Good boy.
- 好孩子 - 老天
- Good boy. - Oh, my God.
丘比特要杀光他们！
Jupiter's going to finish them off.
你为什么要杀我们？
Why are you doing this to us?
为什么要这么做？你听到了吗？
Why are you doing this? You hear me?
把我的孩子还给我
Give me back my baby!
你到底想要我们什么？
What the fuck do you want from us?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
把我的小女孩还给我 你听到了吗？
You give me back my little girl. You hear me?
鲍比
Bobby?
你还剩下多少子弹？
How many bullets do you have left?
还有一个半弹夹
A clip and a half.
我们怎么办？
What are we doing?
走哪边 野兽？哪条路？快 跟着血迹
Which way, Beast? Which way? Come on. Follow the trail.
来吧 大块头
Come on, big guy. I hope you're not afraid of the dark.
我希望你可不是害怕黑暗
他们在哪 孩子？
Where are they, boy?
往哪走 野兽？
Which way, Beast?
好孩子
Good boy.
鲍比？
Bobby?
鲍比 我跟着血迹走
Bobby, I followed the blood trail.
到了一个地方象是什么小镇 鲍比？
It leads to a town or something out here. Bobby?
谁知道呢？也许有人会听到我们的呼叫
Who knows? Maybe someone heard our calls.
没有人会听到我们的呼叫 布伦达！
Nobody's gonna hear the fucking calls, Brenda!
没有人能看到这混蛋沙漠里的烟！
Nobody's gonna see the goddamn smoke in this goddamn desert!
我们在这个他妈的… 妈的！
We're in the middle of freakir… Ah, shit!
老天！
God!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我太害怕了
I'm so scared.
那些人是什么人？
Who are these people?
好狗狗 呆着别动
Good dog. Stay.
- 你推她了？- 是的
- Did you push her? - Yes.
- 你把家具砸烂了？- 没有
- Did you destroy the furniture? - No.
你管她叫大篷车垃圾？
Did you call her trailer park trash?
- 那么你是说你还… - 我还爱着她
- So, now, you're saying you still… - I'm still in love with her.
好了 但是…你说你珍惜婚姻
Okay, but… So, you said you treasured the marriage…
然后就在结婚两周后 决定离婚？
And you wanted to end it two weeks after you got into it?
我想结束这段婚姻 是因为我…
I wanted to end it because I have…
我有种感觉就是 我们过不到一块去
I had a feeling that things werert gonna work together.
她根本就不跟我合作 我想训练她…
She wasrt working as a team player with me, and I tried coaching her…
- 你怎么训练她的？- 我就是…
- What were you doing coaching her? - Well, I tried to show…
- 她是你的孩子吗？- 不 不是 但是
- Is she your child? - No, she's not my child, but she…
她想让我吃晚饭 吃意大利面
She wanted me to eat dinner… spaghetti…
我想在面条凉了前就做
And I wanted to do it before it got cold.
小心她的头 鲍比
Watch her head, Bobby.
来吧
Come on.
我女儿在哪？她在哪？
Where's my daughter? Where is she?
回答我！
Answer me!
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is.
我从来没有离开这里一步
I never leave this place.
你们让我们这些家
Your people asked our families…
离开我们的镇…
To leave their town…
然后你们毁掉了我们的家
And you destroyed our homes.
我们就到了矿井
We went into the mines.
你们又引爆炸弹
You set off your bombs…
把一切都烧成灰烬
And turned everything to ashes.
是你们让我们变成这个样子
You made us what we've become.
梆！梆！梆…
Boom. Boom. Boom!
我的孩子在哪？
Where's my baby?
有什么让你这么高兴的？
What's so funny?
早餐时间到了
It's breakfast time!
请不要杀我
Please don't kill me.
「请不要杀我」
"Please don't kill me."
- 请不要杀我 - 「请不要杀我」
- Please don't kill me. - "Please don't kill me."
蜥蜴
Lizard.
把孩子杀掉
Kill the baby.
孩子 孩子
Baby. Baby.
鲁比 你让开
Get out of the way, Ruby.
我说让开 马上让开！
I said get. Now, get!
先生 你要和我们一起玩吗？
Mister, would you play with us?
鲁比！
Ruby!
凯瑟琳！
Catherine!
好了
It's okay.
没事了 会好的
It's okay. We'll be all right.
好了
It's okay.
不 不
No. No.
- 来 来 - 不！
- Come on. Come on. - No!
- 来 布伦达！- 鲍比！
- Come on, Brenda. - Bobby!
跟着我 跟着我 跟着我
Stay with me. Stay with me. Stay with me.
跟上 一切会好的
Come on. Come on. It's gonna be all right.
会好的
It'll be all right.
小心 请一定小心
Careful. Please? Please?
妈的
Oh, shit.
滚出来 混蛋
Come on out, you motherfucker.
看 只是个风滚草
Look. Look. It's just a tumbleweed. Come on.
走吧 我们回车里去吧
Come on. Let's go back to the trailer. Come on.
快点
Come on. Come on.
啊 老天！
Oh, my God!
- 老天！- 她不见了！
- Oh, my God! - She's gone.
她不见了！不见了！布伦达！布伦达！快去车里准备好！
She's fucking gone! She's gone! Brenda! Brenda! Go get the trailer ready.
- 布伦达 去准备… - 妈妈在哪？
- Brenda, go get the… - Where's Mom?
- 去车里准备 好不好？- 妈妈在哪？
- Go get the trailer ready. Okay? - Where's Mom?
- 妈妈在哪？- 听我说 你现在要去车里
- Where's Mom? - Listen to me. I need you to go get the trailer.
然后按我们商量的来做
Just go in, do what we talked about.
我们走！从窗走！从窗走！
Let's go! Get the window! Get the window!
窗户卡住了！
It's stuck!
鲍勃！救我！
Bob! Help me! Bob!
快快快快快！快出去！
Go! Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go! Get out!
给你
Here.
鲁比！
Ruby!
鲁比！回来！
Ruby! Come back here!
你这个小骚货！
You little bitch!
把孩子给我！
Give me that baby!
我操！
Fuck!
来吧 我们离开这里
Come on. Let's get out of here.
啊 老天！看！是鲍勃！
Oh, my God. Look! Bobby!